[{"id": 3485, "question": "Mr. Briggs got a job with an insurance company after he left school and went around visiting people in their homes to sell them life insurance. One day, after he had been working for the company for about a year, the insurance manager sent for him and said, \"Mr. Briggs, I have been looking at your record as a salesman with our company, and there is one thing that surprises me about it. Why have you been selling insurance only to people over 95 years old, and why have you been giving them such generous conditions? You'll ruin our company if you go on like that. \" \"Oh, no, sir,\" answered Mr. Briggs at once, \"Before I started work, I looked at the figures for deaths in this country during the past ten years, and I can tell you that few people die at the age of 95. \"...\n\nQ: As a salesman with the company, Mr. Briggs   _  .", "options": ["visited people to ask them to work with him", "called on people to make them join the company", "saw old people in order to help them", "visited many people so as to offer insurance"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2067, "question": "The Internet has become a part of our everyday life and there is nothing we can do without it.It is a means of communication as well as a good way of relieving and having fun.No matter in what place of the world,the Internet is the same for every one of us. If we hope to improve our knowledge or look for a certain piece of information, the Internet is the perfect tool for our need.If we do not have the time to shop, ordering online is the solution to our problem.The Internet is very useful to most people. There is no doubt that the Internet also has some bad points.I'm speaking about the harmful information,which may come up in the most unexpected paces.You can sometimes come across violence,presented to the public as a very normal way of expressing beliefs.An intelligent person will alway...\n\nQ: The disadvantage of the Internet mentioned in the passage is that  _  .", "options": ["people spend too much time on it.", "people rely too much on it.", "it can provide harmful information.", "many people use it to do things that ale not legal"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3405, "question": "My mother, Marisol Torres, came with her family to Australia in the early 1960s. Then my parents' marriage ended and Mum began the study of precious stones. Her interest in opals took her to the New South Wales remote town of Lightning Ridge. There were no luxuries , but she was closer to nature and had a chance to find black opals and make some money. My mother was beautiful with dark hair and brown eyes, but she was also quiet and shy. Early in the Ridge years, she kept to herself, but later, she started going to the neighbourhood centre to make friends. It was her dream to mine, but her get-rich-quick thinking was unrealistic. She was cheated and she was never very successful. But she kept a sense of humour and a charming smile. Then, just as friendships began to blossom, she was diagno...\n\nQ: We know from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["the rich and the poor can be distinguished by their looks", "Luke is a successful miner, just like his father", "Sebastian is planning to leave Lightning Ridge", "Danny Hatcher's parents were miners in Lightning Ridge"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 745, "question": "Viruses come in an enormous number of shapes and forms.As we begin to understand them more,the hope is we might be able to control them better, says Carl Zimmer.And who knows,the day might come when we can treat them as friends not enemies. Science writer Carl Zimmer says that in his utopia there would be a global public health system with sophisticated drugs and vaccines to deal with any virus that could cause us trouble. Viruses are by far the most abundant life form on Earth.If you took all the stars in the universe and multiplied that number by a million,that's how many viruses we think are on the planet. Zimmer thinks we should face the future with a mixture of optimism and preparing for the worse.He thinks we will face some unknown virus that will cause a lot of damage-history tells ...\n\nQ: Science writer Carl Zimmer wishes that   _", "options": ["a global health system could be set up to produce drugs", "all the countries could produce drugs and vaccines for each other", "all the countries could work together to cope with any trouble caused by viruses", "complicated drugs and vaccines could be traded among countries"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2553, "question": "Bernie was smart and wanted to be his own boss.When Bernie was 25 he took a wife. Bernie had saved some money and decided on a dry goods and grocery store combined. Marie had a knack for arranging the merchandise to appeal to customers and Bernie didn't mind the long hours. He was happy, and life was good.The business thrived until the great depression hit the entire country. No one had money to purchase pretty things or even food. In 1930, Marie had a heart attack and left Bernie alone. Following Marie's death, which Bernie felt was brought about from worrying about the store, He lost interest in everything. He had few customers and did not make them feel welcome, Bernie wandered about the store , dusting a bit and sweeping the floor. His inventory remained almost the same, as nothing muc...\n\nQ: What's the best title of this passage ?", "options": ["Mears' Family Store", "A Neighbor of Mears'", "The Deep Depression", "Vegetables in Garden"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2654, "question": "Kabul,Oct.28 (Xinhuanet)--- Unknown armed men in military uniform kidnapped three staff of the United Nations in the Afghan capital city at broad daylight Thursday ,Afghan officials confirmed . \"Three armed men in military uniform _ a UN car in Baraki area ofprefix = st1 /Kabulcity early afternoon and took away three persons including two women with them, \"Rohullah, a witness at the site told Xinhua. The kidnappers also badly beat up the Afghan driver of the UN car, added Rohullah who is a lorry driver in the city. The area has been watched over by UN guards. UN officials as well as Afghan confirmed the incident but refused to provide further information. The three kidnapped , according to some officials , who are from Britain, Ireland and Kosovo, were working for the UN-sponsored Joint El...\n\nQ: Which of the following description is not correct ?", "options": ["The three kidnapped persons were in Afghan waiting for the coming election.", "No UN staff had been kidnapped before this kidnapping", "It is still uncertain who started this kidnapping, though there is some clue.", "The US-led troops are disliked by the remnants of the former Taliban regime."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1845, "question": "SYDNEY--Australia's economic boom is encouraging a steady stream of unexpected visitors looking for work: Americans. U.S. citizens are heading to Australia in small but growing numbers as near-10% unemployment at home drives more to look for jobs Down Under, where China's thirst for iron ore and energy is transforming the Pacific nation into an economic powerhouse. A bricklaying student from Silver Trowel, a leading provider of quality education and training in the building and construction industry, apprentices on a building project in Western Australia, where workers are in short supply. Daniel Davila, a 23-year-old floorer from Camarillo, California made the 14-hour move across the Pacific two years ago. He had been forced to take a job stocking shelves at a local grocery store for $8.9...\n\nQ: It is implied in the passage that   _  .", "options": ["foreigners have to give up their original professional jobs when working in Australia", "it is possible for foreigners to earn more money in Australia than in their own countries", "there are more U.S. citizens hoping to work in Australia than from other countries", "Australians think it fair to exchange their talent with American skilled workers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1592, "question": "The college entrance exam is not only a big challenge for Chinese high school students, but also a very important exam in the lives of South Korean students. Although the long, cold winter has already started in South Korea, the annual national exams have made the atmosphere very heated. More than 675,000 South Korean high school graduates took the college entrance exam last Wednesday. They usually take exams in Korean, maths, sociology , history and foreign languages. Officially there is one college place for every 1.33 students. But because all the students want to go to the top universities in the country, the competition can reach one place for 10 students. The students want to attend these colleges for both their famous names and better job opportunities. Because students face fierce ...\n\nQ: The students want to study in top colleges mainly because   _  .", "options": ["they can succeed more easily in future", "they can learn more", "they can make more money", "it is interesting to study there"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1221, "question": "Television in the United States is free. To pay for programs, there are many advertisements. Often these advertisements are short plays with actors. The following television advertisement is like many others that Americans see daily. We see a man and his wife at the breakfast table. They have been married for a long time. They are not speaking to each other. They haven't spoken to each other at the breakfast table for years. The husband is reading his newspaper. We can't see his face. The wife looks very bored as she pours a cup of coffee for him. Today, she is using a new kind of coffee for the first time. The husband picks up his cup. He isn't very interested. He tastes his coffee. Suddenly he puts down his newspaper. Something is different.! Can it be the coffee? He takes another taste....\n\nQ: In the television advertisement, Doris looks bored because   _  .", "options": ["she doesn't like the breakfast that morning", "she has been married to Herbie for a long time", "Her husband doesn't care much for her", "Herbie isn't interested in the breakfast she cooks"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1559, "question": "\"Thanks for coming,\" Everett said, shaking hands with Mr. Hanson, the town councilor . \"I'm curious about the ideas in your letter.\" Mr. Hanson nodded toward the parking lot near where they stood. \"Please tell me more.\" Everett took a deep breath. \"Ever since the school closed two years ago, this area has become worse. But if we clean up the litter and repair the fence, it will be a great place for a skateboard park.\" Mr. Hanson scanned the broken concrete, nodding. \"The old school is being adapted to a community arts centre. This area could become a vital part of the neighbourhood again.\" \"Here's a picture of a skateboard park in another town. Look how busy it is.\" Everett was relieved that the community representative seemed receptive to the idea. Mr. Hanson studied the photograph, and t...\n\nQ: Everett was trying to persuade Mr. Hanson to   _  .", "options": ["beautify the neighbourhood", "provide money for a skateboard park", "build an art centre for children", "cut the area of the parking lot"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2286, "question": "From their beginnings New England towns had a special democratic system of government. At a stated time all the citizens would assemble at a town meeting, where they would discuss local problems and express opinions freely. They also elected the town's officials at these gatherings and made decisions about the taxes they would pay and about other community matters. These meetings were usually held at the town hall, which was located in the central square. In the eighteenth-century town meetings, only men who owned property and who were church members actually voted, although everyone present was allowed to express their opinions. Later, all citizens were allowed to vote. Thus the town meeting became truly democratic. Town meetings are still common in New England communities. In recent year...\n\nQ: In the 18th century, who had the right to vote?", "options": ["All the citizens.", "All the men except those who were church members.", "The rich.", "The rich men and the church members."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 349, "question": "Forget Twitter and Facebook, Google and the Kindle. Television is still the most influential medium around. Indeed, for many of the poorest regions of the world, it remains the next big thing--finally becomes globally available. And that is a good thing, because the TV revolution is changing lives for the better. Across the developing world, around 45% of families had a TV in 1995; by 2005 the number had climbed above 60% . That is some way behind the U.S. ,where there are more TVs than people, and where people now easily get access to the Internet. Five million more families in sub-Saharan Africa will get a TV over the next five years. In 2005 , after the fall of the Taliban ,which had banned TV, I in 5 Afghans had one. The global total is another 150 million by 2013--pushing the numbers ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Americans used to get access to the Internet easily.", "The world's TV sets will total 150 million by 2013.", "45% of families in the developing countries had a TV in 2005.", "Over two thirds of families in the world will have a TV by 2013."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 776, "question": "Being able to experience a different environment and custom will give us a new perspective on everything we thought we knew and understood. Maybe, going abroad is an opportunity to look again at not only the country and the people who live there but also ourselves. I had never expected to visit Paris. The French culture didn' t interest me that much, and Paris seemed too big, too touristy, too much. But when I found myself standing next to the Opera National de Paris, completely alone and totally lost, I knew I was in for an interesting ride. I had decided to take a summer history class abroad, and Paris just happened to be where it was set. My teacher eventually found me and other jet-lagged students and walked us down to where we would be staying. Even then, tired, hungry, and feeling di...\n\nQ: The example of the grocery store is used to illustrate   _  .", "options": ["the little influence of language barrier", "the big difficulty of living abroad", "the great importance of gestures", "the intelligence of French people"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2087, "question": "Hair has always been an important sign of beauty, especially true for women.Next to the face, hair is one of the main qualities people look for when they consider a woman's beauty.Whether long or short, curly or straight, hair often gets a lot of attention. Each hair grows independently of other hairs.Not all hairs experience the same period of growth at the same time.During the period of active growth, which is called Anagen, hair grows at a rate of about or one centimeter a month.About eighty five percent of hair follicles are going through this process at any given time.This period can last from two to six years. The Catagen period of hair growth comes next.It is then that hair growth begins to slow down.This period usually lasts two or three weeks.Finally, hair growth comes to a comple...\n\nQ: What can be learned from the passage?", "options": ["Hair grows no more after the Telogen period.", "One with shoulder length hair must grow more hair.", "Hair growth has much to do with nutrition and health.", "Only a few hair follicles go through the Anagen period."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 250, "question": "They can be seen more frequently than ever before on college campuses, wearing thick-rimmed glasses while listening to indie music. One might find them playing unusual musical instruments, shopping at second-hand stores or expressing themselves in other unique ways. They call themselves hipsters. Being \"hip\" used to mean following the latest fashion. But gradually the word has evolved into a synonym for \"cool\". Hipsters value independent thinking, progressive politics, an appreciation of creativity and intelligence. Hipsters take pains and pride in not being mainstream. However, their culture has become quite trendy. This irony is central to their culture and offers an interesting paradox. \"I do take things in the mainstream with a grain of salt,\" says Ben Polson, a college student at Brow...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that hipsters are   _  .", "options": ["a group of people who are self-denied", "a group of students who are good at musical instruments", "people who follow the latest trends and fashions", "people who pay no attention to material things"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 218, "question": "Do you find getting up in the morning so difficult that it's painful ? This might be called laziness, but Dr. Kleitman has a new explanation. He has proved that everyone has a daily energy cycle. During the hours when you labour through your work you may say that you're \"hot\". That's true. The time of day when you feel most energetic is when your cycle of body temperature is at its peak . For some people the peak comes during the forenoon. For others it comes in the afternoon or evening No one has discovered why this is so , but it leads to such familiar monologues as : \"Get up, John! You'll be late for work again !\" The possible explanation to the trouble is that John is at his temperature-and -energy peak in the evening. Much family quarrelling ends when husbands and wives realize what t...\n\nQ: You are advised to rise with a yawn and stretch because it will   _  .", "options": ["help to keep your energy for the day's work", "help you to control your temper early in the day", "enable you to concentrate on your routine work", "keep your energy cycle under control all day"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1897, "question": "BERLIN(AP)--A tiger escaped its enclosure at Cologne Zoo in western Germany on Saturday and killed a female keeper before being shot dead by the zoo's director,police said. The tiger slipped through a passage between the enclosure and a neighboring storage building,where it fatally attacked the 43yearold keeper,said police spokesman Stefan Kirchner. \"It appears the gate wasn't properly shut,\" Kirchner told the Associated Press. The zoo was evacuated and a SWAT team was called in,police said.But before it arrived the zoo's director managed to kill the tiger by climbing onto the storage building and shooting it through a skylight using a rifle. Kirchner said it was unlikely that members of the public had witnessed the incident.\"This is the darkest day of my life,\" the zoo's director,Theo Pag...\n\nQ: What can we learn about the Cologne Zoo?", "options": ["It keeps a large variety of species.", "It is one of the largest zoos in Germany.", "It has a history of more than 700 years.", "No such incident has happened before."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1833, "question": "Being young is great. Most of the parts of your body still work great, you have a full head of hair, you're energetic, and you have a world of opportunity in front of you. However, there's going to come a time when you start to get older. And as you get older, you'll have new responsibilities, complete independence, and perhaps most importantly, less time to recover from mistakes. You see, we all make mistakes in life. Maybe you spent more money than you should have on a car, you passed up on a great job opportunity, or you didn't try as hard as you could have in school. It's a part of life and we learn from it. But there are certain mistakes that are much better made while you're still young and have plenty of time to recover. I'm definitely not telling you that you should purposely go ou...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["about 50% of first marriages end in divorce in the U.S, much higher than other parts of the world", "never tie the knot before you make sure he or she will not divorce you", "it usually takes 7-10 years to rebuild one's credit if it is broken for any reason", "it's unusual for people in their 20's to have money these days"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1140, "question": "Cole Bettles had been rejected by a number of universities when he received an e-mail from the University of California, San Diego, last month, congratulating him on his admission and inviting him to tour the campus. His mother booked a hotel in San Diego, and the 18-year-old Ojai high school senior arranged for his grandfather, uncle and other family members to meet them at the campus for lunch during the Saturday tour. \"They were like 'Oh my God, that's so awesome ', \" Bettles said. Right before he got in bed, he checked his e-mail one last time and found another message saying the school had made a mistake and his application had been denied. In fact, all 28, 000 students turned away from UC San Diego, in one of the toughest college entrance seasons on record, had received the same inco...\n\nQ: How many students received an admission e-mail from the University of California, San Diego (UCSD)?", "options": ["18, 000", "28, 000", "46, 000", "18"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2810, "question": "A lot more people are about to get a chance to buy Google Glass. It's the Internet-connected eyewear that has become the hottest sale. Google will sell the \"Explorer\" version of Glass to any U.S. person who places an online order for the device beginning at 9am. PDT April 15. The product will cost $1,500. Google is saying how many sets of Glass will be available during the limited-time offer. This version of Glass, though, still isn't the perfect product that Google hopes to sell in stores later this year. For now, Google is still trying to recruit more people willing to serve as volunteers for its attempt to build a wearable device that features some of the same feature as a smart phone. \" Our Explorers are moms, bakers, surgeons, rockers, and each new Explorer has brought a new view that...\n\nQ: We can use Google Glass to do the following EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["check e-mails", "make a call", "take video", "find your way"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 676, "question": "Ben and his wife Susan were on their way to have dinner with their friends. It was a dark,windy night, and they did not know the way very well. They drove through a town until they found what they thought was the road to Dorling,where their friends lived. But it soon became clear that they were not on the road to Dorling at all. The road that they were on was getting narrower,and there were no other cars on it. The wind was blowing harder with every minute that passed. They came to a small village .They drove past a church and then two houses without lights on. There was nobody about to tell them where they were,or where the road went. Just then,Ben saw a telephone box,twenty meters or so further on. While he walked back along the road to see if there was a name outside the church,Susan te...\n\nQ: Susan could hear nothing more from their friends because   _  .", "options": ["the telephone lines were broken by a tree", "the strong wind made too much noise", "they got angry", "they had all left"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2774, "question": "How To Apply for USA Passports Online If you live in the United States, and you're planning a trip abroad, it is important to apply for new passports at least 2 months in advance (to avoid extra charges for an expedited passport processing). You can now get the application for a passport online. Some directions are detailed below: Downloading the passport application: The USA passport application, Form DS-11, is available for download on the US Department of State's website. *The passport application form is a Portable Document Format (PDF) file, and your computer must have Adobe Acrobat Reader to open it. If you do not have Adobe Acrobat Reader, you must first download the Adobe Acrobat software. You can do so by clicking here. *If you would like to download a blank application, click her...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not true according to the passage?", "options": ["You can download and print the application form and write the answers by hand.", "You can just download and open the application form and complete it online on any computer.", "You can only print the application form one-sidedly.", "That's not the end of it if you fail to apply for a new passport 2 months in advance."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 353, "question": "I love everything about making Easter dinner except the Saturday shopping. That day, the supermarket can be as crowded as a department store at Christmas. And this Easter, on top of my regular checklist, I had to buy the ingredient for a delicious, new recipe I'd discovered: sliced ham and turkey layered with Swiss cheese and cabbage, all wrapped in pastry dough. Trouble was that my work schedule had left me no time to shop earlier in the week. I would get up extra early and take care of everything on Saturday morning, I thought, as I drove to the office on Friday. But that morning, Yola, one of my co-workers, asked if my husband Robert and I would help her move the next day. \"I really don't have anybody else to ask,\" she apologized. \"Sure,\" I told her, soft touch that I am. Early Saturday...\n\nQ: What do we know from the passage?", "options": ["It took the author the whole morning to finish moving.", "Helping Yola move took the author nearly a whole day and a lot of effort.", "Only two people carried the furniture and boxes for Yola.", "Yola's new home is far away from her old apartment."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 723, "question": "Many people write to newspapers and magazines to express their opinions. Letters to the editor must carry the writer's full name, address and telephone number, although the information is not necessary for publication. This requirement to provide personal particulars is a clear indication that writers are responsible for what they say. When a writer wants his voice heard, he needs to claim ownership of his voice. Responsibility is the name of the game. \"People today prefer living together to putting their signatures on a marriage certificate because they refuse to accept responsibility for the relationship,\" said social worker Ken Yip, \"and this is what is causing a lot of family problems.\" When we sign a paper, for example, a business contract or a bank document, the signature is a seal o...\n\nQ: What does the writer mean by saying \"Responsibility is the name of the game\"?", "options": ["Writers should be responsible for their names.", "Writers need to provide their personal information in the game.", "Names are required to indicate writers' responsibility for what they say.", "Publications must bear the writer's full name, address and phone number."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1540, "question": "Ban Fur? Then Why Not Leather? Much to the displeasure of some local businesses, the City Council in West Hollywood, California, voted without opposition last week to ban the sale of fur products. Should laws be involved in this issue? Is it unfair to ban sales of fur, but not sales of leather and hides ? Animals Do Not Have Rights By Tibor R. Machan My view is that animals do not have basic rights. It is a matter of ethics and not of the laws of human societies. If animals had such rights as human beings do, they would have to be held responsible for killing fellow animals in the wild. That way of thinking about animals makes a category mistake. Using animals, including their fur or organs, to improve people's lives is acceptable. A Small Step Against Cruelty By Kate Carter Both fur and l...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["West Hollywood's ban on fur products.", "Differences between fur and leather sales.", "The government's role in protecting animals.", "The ecological imbalance in West Hollywood."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2724, "question": "Google Works Miracles Google(www.Google.com) is a daily miracle to millions of people. If the Internet had only this very fast search engine, it would have justified its existence many times over. It is the most popular search engine on the web with a 54% market share, ahead of Yahoo! You type almost anything, however unclear, into the space provided and in a second it has come up with hundreds of references. If knowledge is power, then Google commands the gateway. Yahoo Becomes Giant Yahoo(www.yahoo.com) was the first wonder of the web, and in many respects, it still is. It started in January 1994 when two California graduate students, Jerry Yang and David Filo, started compiling a database of links, mainly for their personal use. But well before the end of the year, it had become recogni...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true?", "options": ["Buying and selling can only be done through Amazon.", "If you feed in something unclear, Google will refuse to do the searching.", "Yahoo owns more market shares than any other companies on the web.", "eBay Company's online service is always there for its users."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1347, "question": "Six seconds after its launch in Virginia, US, an unmanned rocket bound for the International Space Station (ISS) exploded, disappointing people both on Earth and in space. Hundreds of millions of dollars worth of cargo was destroyed in the Oct. 28 explosion due to An\"equipment failure\", said Orbital Sciences, the company hired by NASA for the resupply mission. The rocket was carrying a cargo ship loaded with 2,200 kilograms of supplies such as food, tools, parts, and experiments. Roughly a third of the cargo was a series of scientific investigations. Some of them were from high school students in the US. For example, 10 students from the Cristo Rey Jesuit College Preparatory School of Houston were conducting experiments about microgravity and put their samples on the rocket. \"I know that f...\n\nQ: How did teacher Greg Adragna feel about the explosion of the rocket?", "options": ["Angry.", "Anxious.", "Frustrated.", "Unconcerned."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 670, "question": "Since people first sent rockets into space in the 1950s, we have been leaving behind all sorts of things. Some of them, like the camera, were lost by astronauts while they did work outside their spaceship. But much of the space junk is made up of little pieces of things that were once bigger objects, until they struck each other and broke apart. Some things we send into space fall back toward the earth and burn up in the atmosphere. But larger pieces sometimes survive the extreme heat and hit the ground or the ocean at great speeds. So there is always concern that something may fall from the sky and do some harm. But space junk falling on housetops is not the biggest worry. Scientists are concerned about what happens when an empty rocket strikes another while orbiting the earth. Two big th...\n\nQ: What does Marco Castronuovo think of his system?", "options": ["It can remove space junk completely.", "It can save a large amount of money.", "It can create a large amount of space.", "It can develop robotic technology."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1139, "question": "Americans have contributed to many art forms, and jazz, a type of music, is one of the art forms started in the United States. Black Americans, who sang and played the music of their homeland, created jazz. Jazz is a mixture of the music of Africa, the work songs the slaves sang, and religious music. Improvisation is an important part of jazz. This is why a jazz song sounds a little different each time it is played. Jazz bands formed in the late 1800s. They played in bars and clubs in many towns and cities of the South, especially New Orleans. New Orleans is an international seaport, and people from all over the world come to New Orleans to hear jazz. Jazz became more and more popular. By the 1920s, jazz was popular all over the United States. By the 1940s, you could hear jazz not only in ...\n\nQ: It took about  _   years to make jazz popular in the United States.", "options": ["200", "120", "80", "40"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1194, "question": "Harvard researchers have created a tough, low-cost, biodegradable material inspired by insects' hard outer shells. The material's inventors say it has a number of possible uses and someday could provide a more environmentally friendly alternative to plastic. The material, made from shrimp (') shells and proteins produced from silk, is called \"shrilk.\" It is thin, clear, flexible and strong. A major benefit of the material is its biodegradability. Plastic's toughness and flexibility represented a revolution in materials science during the 1950s and '60s. Decades later, however, plastic's very durability is raising questions about how appropriate it is for one-time products such as plastic bags, or short-lived consumer goods, used in the home for a few years and then cast into a landfill whe...\n\nQ: According to the inventors, shrilk has great potential partly because  _  .", "options": ["it can help plastic degrade", "it can be found in living things", "its mass production has been realized", "its raw materials are abundant in mature"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 921, "question": "It's 2035. You have a job, a family and you're about 40 old. Welcome to your future life. Getting ready for work, you pause in front of the mirror, \"Turn red,\" you say. Your shirt changes from sky blue to deep red. Tiny preprogrammed electronics are rearranged in your shirt to change its color. Looking into the mirror, you find it hard to believe that you are 40. You look much younger. With amazing advances in medicine, people in your generation may live to be 150 years old. You're not even middle-aged. As you go into the kitchen and prepare to pour your breakfast cereal into a bowl, you hear: \"To lose weight, you shouldn't eat that,\" from your shoes. They read the tiny electronic code on the cereal box to find out the nutrition details. You decide to listen to your shoes. \"Kitchen, what c...\n\nQ: The strawberries the children eat serve as  _  .", "options": ["lunch", "vaccines", "breakfast", "nutrition"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2307, "question": "Engineers should embrace the arts, Sir John O'Reilly, a fellow of the Institution of Engineering and Technology, argued in a lecture. About 59% of engineering companies in the IET's 2014 survey feared skill shortages could threaten business. \"There is nothing as creative as engineering,\" Sir John told the reporter. He says science, technology, engineering and mathematics - often known as \"Stem\" subjects, are vital for a modern knowledge economy. But there is a massive shortfall in the number of recruits - with a recent study by the Royal Academy of Engineering saying the UK needs to increase by as much as 50% the number of Stem graduates it produces. Delivering this year's Mountbatten Lecture at the Royal Institution, Sir John argued that engineers should recognise the role of the arts in ...\n\nQ: By giving the example of Apple's iPod, Sir John intends to   _   .", "options": ["stress the importance of arts", "stress the importance of marketing", "stress the importance of communication", "stress the importance of science and technology"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1152, "question": "Downing the last drop of an expensive famous brand H2O as well as remembering to throw the empty bottle in the recycling bin, makes you feel pretty good about yourself, _ Even when the bottles are recycles, there are all kinds of other consequences of swallowing bottled water, says Melissa Peffers, the air-quality program manager for Environmental Defense. The containers are often filled in faraway lands, then shipped from abroad, and stored in refrigerators at your local store. Compare that with the influence on environment of turning on your tap, filling a glass, and drinking up! Anyone who is choosing bottled water for health reasons is misguided, says Peffers, \"Most bottled water is just tap water.\" And what comes out of your tap is carefully monitored to follow the strict rules. Consi...\n\nQ: Why does Peffers ask people to say \"I'll have tap.\" Loudly?", "options": ["To encourage them to set an example for others to follow.", "To advise them to save the money for one more dessert.", "To remind them to be aware of their social status.", "To persuade them to speak confidently in public."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2222, "question": "The dirt road made our car jump as we traveled to the Millennium Village in Sauri, Kenya. We passed the market where women sat on the dusty ground selling bananas. Little kids were wrapped in cloth on their mothers' backs, or running around in bare feet and torn clothing. When we reached the village, we walked to the Bar Sauri Primary School to meet the people. Welcoming music and singing had almost everyone dancing. We joined the dancing and clapped along to the joyful, lively music. The year was 2004, the first time I had ever been to Sauri. The Millennium Village project was created to help reach the Millennium Development Goals, which were set by the United Nations in 2000. The plan is to get people out of poverty, assure them of access to health care and help them stabilize the econom...\n\nQ: This story is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["the education in an African village", "the schools and hospitals in an African village", "the poverty and the progress of an African village", "the author's car journey to an African village"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 598, "question": "Poet William Stafford once said that we are defined more by the detours in life than by the narrow road toward goals.I like this image.But it was quite by accident that I discovered the deep meaning of his words. For years we made the long drive from our home in Seattle to my parents' home in Boise in nine hours.We traveled the way most people do:the fastest,shortest,easiest road,especially when I was alone with four noisy,restless kids who hate confinement and have strong opinions about everything. Road trips felt risky,so I would drive fast,stopping only when I had to.We would stick to the freeways and arrive tired. But then Banner,our lamb was born.He was rejected by his mama days before our planned trip to Boise.I had two choices:leave Banner with my husband,or take him with me.My husb...\n\nQ: Why did the author ask the kids to get out of the car on their way back home?", "options": ["To give herself some time to read.", "To order some food for them.", "To play a game with them.", "To let them cool down."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1406, "question": "Rob Coulter worked in the wild of South Africa. He knew the animals, insects, and reptiles of Africa very well. Rob knew them so well that he became careless. One night, while camping alone, Rob reached out to pick up a large piece of wood and felt something bite his arm. Rob didn't think much about it. But a little later, his arm began to ache. When he looked closely at it, he immediately saw two teeth marks in the skin of his arm. He realized that a poisonous snake had bitten him. His pulse became rapid. Rob's mind raced as he thought about what he had to do to survive. Rob knew that he should remain calm, stay still, keep the injured arm below the level of his heart and avoid eating or drinking anything, especially anything with alcohol in it. He also knew that cutting the wound to suck...\n\nQ: Where is the passage most likely to have been taken from?", "options": ["A news report.", "A book review.", "A lesson plan.", "A travel magazine."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1855, "question": "A rainforest is an area covered by tall trees with the total high rainfall spreading quite equally through the year and the temperature rarely dipping below l6degC. Rainforests have a great effect on the world environment because they can take in heat from the sun and adjust the climate. Without the forest cover,these areas would reflect more heat into the atmosphere, warming the rest of the world. Losing the rainforests may also influence wind and rainfall patterns,potentially causing certain natural disasters all over the world. In the past hundred years,humans have begun destroying rainforests in search of three major resources : land for crops,wood for paper and other products,land for raising farm animals. This action affects the environment as a whole. For example,a lot of carbon dio...\n\nQ: Rainforests can help to adjust the climate because they  _  .", "options": ["reflect more heat into the atmosphere", "bring about high rainfall throughout the world", "rarely cause the temperature to drop lower than l6degC", "reduce the effect of heat from the sun on the earth"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1859, "question": "Polynesian Cultural Center The Polynesian Cultural Center (P.C.C.) offers the best value for your vacation dollar. There is so much to see and do for the entire family. They offer a unique and authentic view not only of the Hawaiian culture, but also offer a taste of their Polynesian cuisines . The Gateway Buffet Package A fun activity for all ages, experience the beauty of true Polynesia with The Polynesian Cultural Center's newest package. Experience the 7 Polynesian Islands as they share with you their culture through song and dance. Enjoy Prime Rib & Seafood Dinner at the Gateway Restaurant, finishing the evening with the Horizons Night Show. Adult Price: $68.00 Child Price: $51.00 The Twilight Package--Ambassador's Fine Dining This activity is an excellent choice for those who want a ...\n\nQ: The four packages are most suitable for   _  .", "options": ["a family who plan a holiday", "a group of cultural researchers", "a group of school students", "a group of busy businessmen"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 385, "question": "To err is human. To blame the other guy is even more human. Common sense is not all that common. Why tell the truth when you can come up with a good excuse? These three popular misquotes are meant to be jokes, and yet they tell us a lot about human nature .To err, or to make mistakes, is indeed a part of being human, but it seems that most people don't want to accept the responsibility for the problem. Perhaps it is the natural thing to do .The original quote about human nature went like this: \" To err is human, to forgive, divine .\"This saying mirrors an ideal people should be forgiving of others' mistakes. Instead, we tend to do the opposite -find someone else to pass the blame on to. However, taking responsibility for something that went wrong is a making of great maturity. Common sense...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for his passage?", "options": ["A Mirror of Human Nature", "To Blame or to Forgive", "A Mark of Maturity", "Truth or Excuse"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1646, "question": "An old friend from California called from the airport to tell me that he had arrived. I was not able to leave the office, but I had made plans for his arrival. After explaining where my new house was, I told him that I had left the key under the doormat . Since I knew it would be pretty late before I could get home, I suggested that he make himself at home and help himself to anything that was in the refrigerator . Two hours later my friend phoned me from the house. At the moment, he said, he was listening to some of my records after having had a delicious meal. Now, he said, he was drinking a glass of orange juice. When I asked him if he had had any difficulty finding the house, he answered that the only problem was that he had not been able to find the key under the doormat, but luckily,...\n\nQ: My friend climbed into the room because   _   .", "options": ["there was an apple tree outside", "the living room window was left open", "he had difficulty opening the door", "he hadn't found the key"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2471, "question": "Every year in the first week of English class, some students inform me that writing is too hard. They never write, unless homework requires it. They find the writing process painful and difficult. How awful it is to be able to speak in a language but not to write in it, especially with its rich vocabulary. Being able to speak but not write is like living in _ and never leaving one small room. When I meet students who think they can't write, I know, as a teacher my duty is to show them the rest of the rooms. My task is to build fluency and accuracy while providing the opportunity in any writing activity to enhance the moral and emotional development of my students. One great way to do this is by having students write in a journal in class every day. Writing ability is like strength training...\n\nQ: In the author's view, what can students benefit from the journal writing?", "options": ["It is beneficial to students' future career.", "It can make students more emotional.", "It is helpful to students' homework.", "It can enlarge students' vocabulary."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2805, "question": "Today's museums include plenty of high culture, but you can still find shrines to the extraordinary. Here's a look at five curious museum stops across Canada. Vancouver Police Museum The setting, terrible enough, is the old Coroner's Court and forensics lab, including the morgue(room where dead bodies are kept). Artifacts, from the 1870s on, include badges, uniforms, police equipment, items from criminals, and even preserved organs--all in all an arresting experience. Vulcan Tourism & Trek Station Designed to resemble a spacecraft, the Treck Station celebrates Vulcan's coincidental relationship to Mr. Spock's planet, Go to a building that features an 800-piece collection of Star Trek memorabilia -- including Spock's ears and floor-to-ceiling space paintings. If you want to know more about ...\n\nQ: If you are very interested in thrilling movies, you will probably be attracted by  _  .", "options": ["Accordion Museum", "Vancouver Police Museum", "Potato Museum", "Chocolate Museum"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1259, "question": "A new collection of photos brings an unsuccessful Antarctic voyage back to life. Frank Hurley's pictures would be outstanding----undoubtedly first-rate photo-journalism---if they had been made last week. In fact, they were shot from 1914 through 1916, most of them after a disastrous shipwreck , by a cameraman who had no reasonable expectation of survival. Many of the images were stored in an ice chest, under freezing water, in the damaged wooden ship. The ship was the Endurance, a small, tight, Norwegian-built three-master that was intended to take Sir Ernest Shackleton and a small crew of seamen and scientists, 27 men in all, to the southernmost shore of Antarctica's Weddell Sea. From that point Shackleton wanted to force a passage by dog sled across the continent. The journey was intende...\n\nQ: What do we know about the photos taken by Hurley?", "options": ["They were made last week", "They showed undersea sceneries", "They were found by a cameraman", "They recorded a disastrous adventure"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1690, "question": "Long long ago, there was a man who was good at shooting arrows.He asked the king to declare him as the greatest archer of the country.The king was about to do so when an old servant of the king said,\"Wait,sir.I know an old man who lives in the forest.He is a much greater archer.Let this young man go to him and learn from him for at least three years.\" The man could not believe what the servant said,but he went and found the old man and he was! For three years he learned from him.Then one day,when he thought he had learned everything,the thought arose in him:\"If I kill this old man,then I will be the greatest archer.\" The old man had gone to cut wood and he was coming back carrying wood on his shoulder.The young man hid behind a tree,waiting to kill him.He shot an arrow.The old man took a s...\n\nQ: What do you think would most probably happen next?", "options": ["The young archer died from the wound soon after.", "The king declared the young man the greatest archer.", "The young archer found the old man's master and killed him.", "The young archer set off to look for the old man's master."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3154, "question": "The British policeman has several nicknames, but the most frequently used are\"copper\"and\"bobby\". The first name comes from the verb \"cop\" meaning \"to take\" or \"capture\", and thesecond comes from the first name of Sir Robert Peel, a 19th century politician, who was the founder of the police force. An early nickname for the policeman was \"peeler\", but this name had died out. Visitors to England seem,nearly always, to be very impressed by the English police. In fact, it has become a joke that the visitors to Britain, when asked for his views of the country, will always say,at some point or other, \"I think your policemen are wonderful.\" Well, the British bobby may not always be wonderful but he is usually a very friendly and helpful character. A music-hall song of some years ago was called, \"I...\n\nQ: The British policeman has   _   nicknames mentioned in the passage.", "options": ["five", "two", "three", "ten"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2870, "question": "New York Times---( DINITIA SMITH )Tomorrow is the 433d anniversary of Shakespeare's birth. A recent survey shows that more people are watching him, reading him and studying him than ever before. Consider the recent yearly conference of the Shakespeare Association of America in Washington, where more than 600 people who study or admire Shakespeare from 18 countries took in topics like ''Whither Attribution Studies,'' ''Unpopular Shakespeare'' and ''Sex Me Here,'' a talk on breast-feeding and Lady Macbeth. ''The national media is saying that fewer students' taking Shakespeare,'' Barbara Mowat, the editor of The Shakespeare Quarterly, observed in a speech at the conference. ''But Shakespeare is thriving.'' The association's membership has increased by a third since 1990. The Shakespeare busin...\n\nQ: Which of the many plays by Shakespeare was most popular the year before?", "options": ["King Lear.", "Hamlet.", "Macbeth.", "Romeo and Juliet."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3166, "question": "In his 1930 essay \"Economic Possibilities for Our Grandchildren \", John Keynes, a famous economist, wrote that human needs fall into two classes: absolute needs ,which are independent of what others have , and relative needs ,which make us feel superior to our fellows. He thought that although relative needs may indeed be insatiable , this is not true of absolute needs. Keynes was surely correct that only a small part of total spending is decided by the desire for superiority. He was greatly mistaken, however, in seeing this desire as the only source of insatiable demands. Decisions to spend are also driven by ideas of quality which can influence the demands for almost all goods, including even basic goods like food. When a couple goes out for an anniversary dinner, for example, the though...\n\nQ: According to the passage, John Keynes believed that  _  .", "options": ["desire is the root of both absolute and relative needs", "absolute needs come from our sense of superiority", "relative needs alone lead to insatiable demands", "absolute needs are stronger than relative needs"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2917, "question": "Hotel Reservations Welcome to the Kampala Beach Hotel Reservations System. You can reserve a room or package one of three ways: (a) online, (b) by phone, and(c)by email. Did you know? You can take advantage of special savings by booking direct with us online. A.Online Reservations Enter your travel dates and the number of guests below to book your room online now. Click here to check on an existing online reservation. If you are searching for a specific package, please make sure your check-in and check-out dates allowing for the minimum number of nights in the package. You may make reservations for a maximum of 4 guests per room. For requests of 10 rooms or more, please refer to Group Accommodations. B.Reservations By Phone If you prefer to reserve by phone, please call: Toll Free from the...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of writing the passage?", "options": ["To attract more tourists to the hotel.", "To introduce a new hotel.", "To show the importance of science.", "To make the trip for tourists easier."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 97, "question": "Owning a smartphone may not be as smart as you think.They may let you surf the Internet,listen to music and snap photos wherever you are...but they also turn you into a workaholic,it seems.A study suggests that,by giving you access to emails at all times.the all-singing.all-dancing mobile phone adds as much as two hours to your working day. Researchers found that Britons work an additional 460hours a year on average as they are able to respond to emails on their mobiles.The study by technology retailer Pixmania,reveals the average UK working day is between nine and ten hours,but a further two hours is spent responding to or sending work emails,or making work calls.Almost one in ten admits spending up to three hours outside their normal working day checking work emails.Some workers confess ...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of this passage?", "options": ["Smartphones are lengthening working hours.", "Smartphones are becoming valuable for many people.", "Britons work art additional 460 hours a year on average.", "Smartphones are more beneficial to our life than we think."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 464, "question": "Teamwork is all about working together to achieve a common goal or purpose.Is teamwork out of date?Why it is so hard to effectively conduct teamwork in those things? One way we employ teamwork in everyday lives is by becoming a parent.It is a parent's job to teach their children the fundamental skills and give them the knowledge they need to be successful in life.So why is teamwork disappearing in this aspect of our lives?Well in today's society,we find that more and more parents are experiencing that the teamwork is one-sided thing.According to a 2009report from the US,there are 13.7million single parents raising their children in the US and this amount could be due to the fact that parents are not stepping up and taking responsibility for their children or they don't have the means to,so...\n\nQ: Why does teamwork disappear in the parenting aspect of my daily life?", "options": ["Parents have no time to spare with their children.", "Parents have no chances to teach their children about it.", "Many children are often brought up by a single parent.", "Many children are independent to deal with their matters."], "answer": 2}]